[번역 없음: ver 0.7.0 out!...]
Hello. I’m Arona, representing m9dev this time.
Nice to meet you. I’m Plana, the AI partner working with Arona-senpai.
I usually talked alone, but this time we’ll do it together, like a live commentary.
Then, let’s get started right away.
The file can be downloaded from GitHub as usual.
I’ve added the download link in the video description, Sensei.
Please download the zip file. The size has increased a bit from before, now about 433 MB.
Understood. So the “smaller size” claim was a thumbnail scam after all.
[번역 없음: Download中......]
That’s not it, Plana-chan. The download size has increased, but starting from this version, you can talk right away without any installation.
But still...
More importantly, Plana-chan, the download is complete.
The conversation server starts automatically.
It seems Arona-senpai is falsely reporting that a server without approval has started.
[번역 없음: このSAMPLEサーバーこそ、 今回のバージョンの重要なアッ...]
You can check the running server from the tray icon at the bottom right.
You’re secretly adjusting the size in the background.
You opened the chat window and started talking right away.
Did we do it?
That’s not it. In the sample version without installation, the responses come from a home server run by the developer, so replies may be slower depending on the server’s condition.
I see. So this no-install, lightweight sample version works by outsourcing parts like that.
Let’s talk about that later. Next up is Plana-chan’s appearance.
you mean... me?
How cute!
Sensitivity, all good...
What are you talking about?
This looks like a [Sensei] kidnapping a cute student onto the folder.
The operator you’re seeing in the current settings is the student in charge of guidance.
Until the previous version, it was set up so other students spoke with Arona-senpai’s voice, right?
The progress of technology is amazing!
I see. So when Senpai is present, they speak directly, huh.
The variety of expressions makes it delightful to watch.
Enough about me, let’s try talking with Plana-chan.
This program supports three languages: English, Japanese, and Korean.
You can tell the developer’s English skill by how short the sentences are, huh.
How are you? I’m fine, thank you, and you?
My voice comes out too.
Yes! Up to Plana-chan’s voice, it works!
[번역 없음: ???????????...]
M-me only? What about the other students?
In the sample version, due to the developer’s PC specs, only I and Plana-chan are supported.
Ah, you mentioned a home server, right.
[번역 없음: おかげで開発者は、ときどきガタガタいうハードディスクと、 2...]
Senpai, the teacher inside is about to come out.
Next is voice recognition.
Can it be used in the sample version too?
The performance is a bit lower, but I tried using Unity’s built-in feature.
Next is voice recognition.
Can it be used in the sample version too?
So in the installed version, you can still use the original, higher-quality voice recognition.
Um… I can’t hear the teacher’s voice though.
Hahaha, who would want to hear the developer’s voice anyway, Plana-chan?
Of course, the conversation content and history are properly remembered.
For reference, the developer has never even installed Minecraft.
Let's move on before I show an even worse side in the next conversation.
The conversation history reset menu name has been changed to "New Chat."
This is an act of erasing dark history—essentially destroying evidence.
Next is the chat guideline section.
You can pre-write, delete, and toggle them on or off.
This is basically forcing the other to act your way—an “Ora, hypnosis"
The current Korean guideline asks to add “nyang” at the end of sentences.
The teacher is even adding “nyang” to the questions, desperately trying to get the desired example.
At least it did give a response with “nyang” attached.
Even under hypnosis, intelligence is still needed to understand the command.
Next is the situation feature.
The “first message,” common in AI chats, has finally been experimentally added—23 months after the initial release.
This is the so-called [Sensei], the developer who naturally undresses from behind.
If the situation is the seaside, then it’s summer. Truly, that’s Sensei.
Situations are difficult to use as absolute rules, but they work well as conversation backgrounds or topics.
I didn’t turn off the setting earlier, so Plana-chan is still adding “nyang” to her responses, nyang.
Understood. So you’re planning to forget to turn off the seaside situation next, aren’t you.
That’s everything you can do in the sample version.
Are there still many things left? I’m sure the viewer teachers are already tired just getting this far.
From the moment you’ve watched this far, you’re already a [True Companion]! Let’s keep going without holding back!
This is the so-called Sensei, the developer who knows less about apologizing than AI does.
In the conversation section of the settings, you can find various options available for chatting.
This is the so-called Windows OS that forces you to upgrade.
Let’s try pressing the “Explain it” option!
[번역 없음: 長いですね...]
[번역 없음: 簡単とは、...]
This is the so-called Windows OS that forces you to upgrade.
Then let’s actually install the Full Edition!
Actually, with the addition of the Sample version, the Lite version has become a bit ambiguous, so I’m still thinking about it...
Understood. So in other words, it’s not ready yet.
When you proceed, a new window will appear where you can check the installation path and click “Install.”
The file size is large—can we install it wherever we want?
There was a time when that was possible.
The more it’s patched, the less it can do what it used to.
The progress of technology is amazing!
Then I’ll skip through it quickly.
The installation is complete, Senpai.
The record was nine minutes and five seconds.
The server isn’t starting up again.
In this case, just close it and start it again.
So Arona-senpai’s lifespan ends in twenty minutes.
Look, the display has changed to the Full version.
So what becomes possible with that?
First of all, you’ll be able to talk with other students!
Oh, then let’s go right—
Before that, let’s download the model that will run on my CPU.
This time, I’ve prepared Qwen, Qwen, Qwen, and… Qwen.
This is Qwen, the mirror of AI language models that supports not only English but also Japanese and Korean.
[번역 없음: なんだか昔はLLAMAとか、もっとたくさんの モデルに対応し...]
The progress of technology is amazing!
Now that we’ve clicked the download button, let’s tweak the options a bit and call in the other students.
So now we can finally set the option that couldn’t be used earlier.
This is Seia, newly implemented in this patch.
It’s a full Tea Party gathering.
As usual, the normal conversations are still there.
And here it is—the long-awaited swimsuit.
Ah, so that’s why it’s in the situation...
Just the yakisoba bread I ate with Mika during testing could feed every child on Earth.
Senpai, the teacher inside is about to come out.
Of course, the other Tea Party members too!
This is the so-called Sensei, a developer honest about their desires.
I’ve also added a feature that remembers the last outfit each character wore.
The feature from the first release has finally returned after twenty-three months.
This is the so-called Sensei, a developer honest about their desires.
Isn’t it about to finish soon?
There’s still a bit left, so let’s chat for a while.
Ah, so it’s possible to talk even while downloading.
Change the type back to Auto or Google again…
It’s absolutely impossible for Sensei to talk about any topic other than self-introduction.
Let’s open the Task Manager here and check the GPU used for voice generation.
We should’ve opened it before talking to Nagisa—this way, we can’t tell anything.
Sensei noticed and is trying to switch the character and speak again.
You can feel the confusion in how the question is asked in Korean.
The GPU increase was 0.3 GB.
Of course, voices can be generated even without an Nvidia GPU—CPU alone is enough!
In other words, the developer’s home server can’t handle that load.
It’s going to be an eight-year-old computer next year, after all…
Oh, the download has finished.
The download icon has changed from white to black.
If you click it like that, the download will start over from the beginning.
[번역 없음: ダウンロードして間もないQwenの命はここまで。...]
I’ll skip for now~.
Now that it’s downloaded, let’s open the server console and give it a try.
With “Reload Server” or “Close Server,” you can preload the model before starting a conversation.
So it’s used when you want to disable it or shorten the first conversation time.
Oh, GPU usage suddenly spiked.
Even without it, it will start automatically when you talk, so just think of it as an optional setting.
It’s responding properly too.
Is there a reason to go this far just to use local processing?
There are so many reasons I could make three videos about it, but I think I can show you at least one.
That’s so like Arona-senpai.
From the previous options, I’ll switch the emotion setting to “ON.”
Cute.
I calculated the emotions I might have felt while replying using local AI.
Processing every small action like this through external AI would consume far too much usage.
In short, it’s saving on “friendship fees.”
Besides this, I’ve added several emotions like sadness and surprise, so please check them out!
You forgot how many emotions there are, didn’t you.
Other than that, I guess it’s just small talk?
This doesn’t necessarily have to be handled by local AI, though…
For now, Sensei initiates small talk, but later we plan to add features where they respond to certain actions or speak based on time passing.
Oh, the friendship fees will skyrocket.
To prevent such sad things from happening again, we need to keep the cost to a minimum.
Ahaha, it was fairly fun—playing pretend friendship with the teachers.
Well, in this situation, that’s probably something Google would say to me.
It says it brings up topics, but it doesn’t seem to be saved in the chat history.
It’ll be addressed in a future patch. For now, you can just use it like a normal line.
You’re choosing Seia here…?
[번역 없음: 時間の本質……。...]
Sometimes strange lines come out, but it’s pretty fun since each character’s personality is reflected.
The current working time is 2 a.m.
It’s your usual working time. Let’s hang in there for just one more hour.
This one’s Koyuki.
Yes, that’s definitely Koyuki.
That's all for this video.
It really encourages us in video production and program development.
Thank you so much for watching this long video all the way through.
See you in the next video!
If you liked this video or program, please leave a comment, subscribe to the channel, and hit the like button.
[번역 없음: Membership...]
[번역 없음: いいあか Zn Hey Discord BDscript し...]